good morning YouTube I am by myself this
morning because Bentley told me
yesterday during our board meeting he is
very busy and so I was like don't don't
worry do your thing come whenever you
can and then I forgot that my brother
was away last week and getting in really
late last night so he said he'd try to
make it be good but he got in at 3 a.m.
that's six hours ago so get some sleep
so I'm just going to go over what I had
said four goals I took on last week and
then my new goals and then cutting it
there because there's no one on video to
crowdsource with and to work on problems
and I'm not really stuck on anything
anyway it's more so I can help other
people find solutions to their problems
which then trigger solutions to my own
problems problems wrong word challenge
so last week I had said I was gonna
continue my personal goals of not
smoking pot doing yoga doing meditation
and smoking daily the only day I did in
scope was Monday I believe because I was
very tired by the time my kid was asleep
and I was very busy that day so just
kept getting moved I had did do all the
other things though so Jamie I do also
took on it was the first week I have
these five conversations every week and
they were all amazing I guess this is
the fifth one it's maybe less amazing
but the board meeting yesterday was
great the future thinkers conversation
on Monday the Omega rural group was
phenomenal I'm so excited for that one
it was posted it was like a three hour
long conversation it was only on it for
an hour of it and then the first idea
Cafe on game B happened and we can't put
the next question and I'm really excited
for Tuesday to have that question which
is why game be individually why do we
want there to be a game be coming on
gaming and I think that's gonna be a
powerful conversation so the other
things I took on were maybe making some
videos for the T other tech explanation
and I actually made four of them
the fourth one being this morning and
that is going well I mean there is
perfect is there gonna be and it's about
putting someone out there can always I
guess anyway and then organizing the
crowd democracy YouTube channel which
honestly I completely forgot about until
it was just reviewing last week's video
and if something I was like like that so
this week I'm going to continue my
personal stuff I may only be attending
three of the five conversations as I
might be escorting my child class on a
field trip to the Nutcracker if there's
still space to volunteer so I won't be
able to attend you make a rule and
Monday seems to be where someone's
coming to visit so I might not be able
to attend the future favors one but the
three that I am directly responsible for
and don't really continue unless I host
them the idea cafe on Tuesday as well as
the board meeting and this on Saturday
are all as far as I know happening so
definitely attending those three
conversations as well as spending an
hour of time organizing my YouTube
channel which will not get it done but
will make a dent in it and that I also
would like to do two more videos for the
together tech explanation I've done so
far that tech is powerful tech is risky
together it's less risky together it's
more powerful and now doing the tools
that we we need to massively collaborate
and then once we have those to do with
just one video and then once we
massively once we have the tools of mass
collaboration what we can create with
them then the sky's the limit we
basically create game be super easily
basically overnight just creates itself
I'm kind of by tapping into our
individual human ingenuity and making
the tools that allow that to happen so
that is what I am taking on in the
coming week and Adriel will definitely
be here next week and perhaps Bentley
and perhaps other people I had reached
out to the game be community to see if
anyone wanted to come on and do this
with me because like what a great
opportunity no one else is showing up
let's see if there's anyone else and but
I did it right before like two hours ago
and the algorithms never really catch up
so there might
someone who reaches out between then and
now between now and next week and maybe
there will be a mysterious other person
joining but that is all I'm going to
cover today that is what I found last
week or cut down didn't get done and
what I am doing you next week thank you
and I will see you here next week for
the board meeting on Friday and the tech
for purpose goal-setting group a week
from today